It's been a while since I was
...up here in front of you maybe i'll stick to the cards
There's been speculation that I was involved in the events
that occurred on the freeway and the rooftop.
I'm sorry, Mr. Stark, but do you
honestly expect us to believe that
that was  bodyguard
in a suit
that conveniently appeared,
despite the fact that you historically despise bodyguards?
Yes.
And this mysterious bodyguard was...
...somehow equipped with...
...an undisclosed Stark high-tech
powered battle suit?
I know that it's confusing.
It is one thing
to question the official story
and another thing entirely to make wild accusations
or insinuate that I'm a superhero.
I mean, let's face it I'm not,
the heroic type.
I've a laundry list of character defects,
all the mistakes that I've made...
largely public.